<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>

<messages>	
	<message>
		<delay>2</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Welcome to #name. JOIN DISCORD, Invite Link In The Server Title.</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>3</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Join our discord READ the TOURIST BOOTH channel... or get stuck and die places often.</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>5</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>HAVING PROBLEMS OPENING DOORS?? Close the game, visit MODS tab in default launcher, right click ZELADOR mod, select REPAIR - No More Problem!</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>7</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Keep getting sick and dying? We use terje mods, Learn more at:  https://tinyurl.com/terje-wiki  </text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>10</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>SOME BUNKERS can become TRAPS join discord, read the tourist booth.</text>
	</message>
	<message>
	<delay>15</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>You Require a Map in inventory to see the map (PRESS M), and a compass in inventory to see 3D markers (PRESS K). Pew Pew Pew!</text>
	</message>
	<message>
	<delay>50</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>We welcome any feedback, please use discord tickets!</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>53</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Test Player Role requires 3 months Of active ticket submissions.</text>
	</message>	
	<message>
		<delay>62</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>All applications for any form of staff or team members begin by applying for Whitelisted role</text>
	</message>	
	<message>
		<delay>75</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Keep our community fun  healthy. No toxic interactions. </text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>85</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>This map is a WORK IN PROGRESS (WIP) Complain at your own risk! LUL...</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>95</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Be your most entertaining and apocalyptic self, but please do not be toxic!</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>100</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Heading into the NB Series BUNKERS? You may need a team. Enter at your own risk!</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>105</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Thank you for helping improve our map! We do Hope you are enjoying your time here with us!</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>115</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>PLEASE DO NOT litter or Loot Cycle. Put it in a fire if you don't want it, or just leave it where it spawned in.</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>170</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Thanks for being part of Zelador! ~ DeGrinchy</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>200</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Not sure what to do? Check our Discord: https://discord.gg/DWXTaEXyUe read the Touris Booth!</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>205</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Issues with door interaction? Close the game, visit MODS tab in default launcher, right click ZELADOR mod, select REPAIR!</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>210</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Join our Discord: https://discord.gg/DWXTaEXyUe</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>215</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>BUNKERs may require a team. Enter at your own risk!</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>220</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Zelador v0.4 Play Test Server open to all dayz players.</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>227</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Submitting tickets or using ZELADOR in your VOD title will help me with map developments, thank you! ~ DeGrinchy</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>230</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Join our Discord: https://discord.gg/DWXTaEXyUe</text>
	</message>
	<message>
		<delay>235</delay>
		<onconnect>1</onconnect>
		<text>Interested in a Test Player Role? U need 3 months Whitelisted, and actively submit no less than 5 tickets/issues in a month.</text>
	</message>	
	<message>
		<deadline>480</deadline>
		<shutdown>1</shutdown>
		<text>NOTICE: #name restarting in #tmin minutes or less.</text>
	</message>
</messages>
